<resources>
    <string name="app_name">group_DecisionBasedGame</string>
    <string name="Ending2">
        I told my father that I had decided to go and deal with the king first before going to the dungeons as I did not want to take any risk of him escaping, he however was not happy with this decision and told me that wouldn’t I rather go and save my mother first to make sure that she’s safe to which I replied sometimes the choices we make, are bigger than ourselves and that putting an end to the tyrannical rule of the king would better improve the kingdom and all the people living in it. My father understood what I had said and told me to immediately go straight to the dungeons to look for my mother afterwards.\n\n
        I rushed through the halls of the castle towards the throne room and as I stood in front of the door and opened it slowly where I was greeted by a giant ball of flame being hurled towards me. I narrowly dodged the incoming spell but was slightly burnt from the intensity of its flames. The last thing that was stopping me from standing in front of the king was the court mage who had been serving the king since his childhood. The final battle to end it once and for all.\n\n
        With the court mage now gone, I finally stood in front of the king and without letting him get any chance to fight back, I drew my sword one more time and thrust it through his chest, ending his life right then and there… I quickly made my way back to the entrance of the dungeons and entered it. I saw all the bodies of the knights who tried to stop my father from freeing my mother and as I closely reached the end of the dungeon what I saw was my father’s cold dead body lying next to another knight in black armor, I wanted to sit there and mourne him for a long time but I didn’t have the time to do that as I had to look for my mother, as I approached my mother’s cell I saw her lying on the floor, scared, I rushed in and immediately checked if she was alive, thankfully she was only unconscious. As I walked through the halls riddled with bodies, my mother wakes up and was happy to see me and asked where my father was, I told her that he died saving you, she laid in my arms speechless and told me that she was sorry for everything that had happened, to which I told her it was okay, and I still loved her. As we exited the dungeon, the clashing of Labyrist members and knights of the king had died down until nothing but silence was left.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="ChoiceD">
        After spending the next 3 weeks studying in the Arlestein Library, I obtained a multitude of knowledge that I used to better enhance the current magic I used through the means of altering the sequences in the casting of the magic itself to further increase the efficiency of the spell itself. This allowed my magical abilities to better aid me in my battles ahead. After I returned from the library and spoke with my father in the Labyrist hideout, he came to me with a dire expression, looking as though there was a major problem that occurred whilst I was away and that was indeed the case. He had apparently sent an expedition down into the hideout’s depths to procure more equipment and items that could be used to further increase our chances in succeeding in our siege of the castle.\n\n
        My father told me that the expedition he sent the day before had yet to return and he was worried for their lives considering they weren’t entirely aware of all the monsters that existed and roamed within the depths of their hideout. So my father asked that I rescue them or at least figure out what happened whilst saying that this would be the trial set for me to see if the knowledge I obtained during my stay in the Arlestein library studying was worth the time spent for it. And so I agreed thinking that it would also be the prime opportunity to make use of the knowledge I obtained in order to find out what happened to the expedition that we lost contact with.\n\n
        As I entered the Labyrist hideout depths, I encountered a number of corpses, and monsters that were wandering around that seemed like the expedition missed out while exploring the area. I took care of them and proceeded to go deeper into the dungeons, after spending a few hours looking for the people who were sent into the dungeon and heard someone from the dark side of the room, to my surprise, it was one of the members who was barely breathing and it seemed he wouldn’t make it, however I reassured him and healed him with the increased magical power of my healing spell. He then told me that they encountered a monster that was unlike what they had seen before and so the rest of the expedition ran away and headed deeper into the dungeon to try and hide from it. I took this information and proceeded into the depths and tried to look for the rest of the members and encountered the monster that fit the description of what the previous person I’d encountered said. A dark lion with a silver mane and golden eyes. As soon as it saw me, it immediately ran towards me and moved at an incredibly fast speed. I thought to myself that I didn’t have the option to run and so I stood my ground and got ready to face the fatal trial ahead of me. As soon as I finished off the monster in front of me, it seemed that the door that it was guarding opened and showed the surviving members of the expedition. They cried out for joy and returned with me back to the main room of the Labyrist headquarters. As the surviving members were being treated, one of them approached me and gave me a book they had found which contained knowledge of stronger offensive magic that I could learn to use and add to my arsenal of magical abilities. We spent the last few days recovering and preparing for the planned attack against the castle and the tyrannical king.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="ChoiceC">
        After speaking with the members of labyrist over the past week, we slowly but surely got to know each other better and learned a lot about their past experiences and the tips they shared that could be used in the middle of combat. As we got to know each other more, we held sparring matches every now and then as a form of training to learn how to better use the abilities and skills I learned from them in a practical battle without any restrictions. In between all the losses, draws and wins, one thing is for sure, and it’s that I definitely gained valuable combat experience that will help me in the coming battles ahead. I approached my father after one of my training sessions and asked him if there was anything I could do to help the members of labyrist to thank them for the help they’ve given me since the time I’ve arrived.\n\n
        My father pondered for a while and came up with an idea, he suggested that I go down into the dungeons and search for the cellars that were said to hold beer and wine alike that can be used to boost the morale of all the members before we leave for the attack on the castle. I thought that it would be a fine idea and agreed to his suggestion, and so I prepared for my descent and faced different monsters before  entering the room that contained the barrels of grog for the party. As I was preparing and making sure that the barrels were intact and filled with what we expected, suddenly I was attacked from behind by a large sewer rat that seemed to be different from the ones I’ve faced, one that was emanating a noxious fume that seemed to be fatal if I fought the monster for too long.\n\n
        After the battle, I took a short break and returned to the main room with my father waiting for my report on what I found in the cellars. After hearing my encounter with the poisonous rat, he was relieved to see that I made it out alive and even happier to hear that the barrels of beer and wine were completely fine after all this time and proceeded to share the news to the members of labyrist. My father sent an expedition group down to the cellars to collect the barrels to bring up in preparation for the party. Later that night we drank and partied to our hearts content and spent the next few days setting up the last preparations we’d need to face the knights and the king in his castle.\n\n

    </string>
    After speaking with the members of labyrist over the past week, we slowly but surely got to know
    each other better and learned a lot about their past experiences and the tips they shared that
    could be used in the middle of combat. As we got to know each other more, we held sparring
    matches every now and then as a form of training to learn how to better use the abilities and
    skills I learned from them in a practical battle without any restrictions. In between all the
    losses, draws and wins, one thing is for sure, and it’s that I definitely gained valuable combat
    experience that will help me in the coming battles ahead. I approached my father after one of my
    training sessions and asked him if there was anything I could do to help the members of labyrist
    to thank them for the help they’ve given me since the time I’ve arrived.
    My father pondered for a while and came up with an idea, he suggested that I go down into the
    dungeons and search for the cellars that were said to hold beer and wine alike that can be used
    to boost the morale of all the members before we leave for the attack on the castle. I thought
    that it would be a fine idea and agreed to his suggestion, and so I prepared for my descent and
    faced different monsters before entering the room that contained the barrels of grog for the
    party. As I was preparing and making sure that the barrels were intact and filled with what we
    expected, suddenly I was attacked from behind by a large sewer rat that seemed to be different
    from the ones I’ve faced, one that was emanating a noxious fume that seemed to be fatal if I
    fought the monster for too long.
    After the battle, I took a short break and returned to the main room with my father waiting for
    my report on what I found in the cellars. After hearing my encounter with the poisonous rat, he
    was relieved to see that I made it out alive and even happier to hear that the barrels of beer
    and wine were completely fine after all this time and proceeded to share the news to the members
    of labyrist. My father sent an expedition group down to the cellars to collect the barrels to
    bring up in preparation for the party. Later that night we drank and partied to our hearts
    content and spent the next few days setting up the last preparations we’d need to face the
    knights and the king in his castle.

    <string name="ChoiceB">
        After spending a long time isolated in my room, meditating and honing my magical powers, I felt as though I had more control over my magic than I once had before I started meditating two weeks ago. I came out of my room and put my strengthened magical abilities to the test. I went to the training room and used my abilities on a training dummy and showed the improvements I’ve made over the past 2 weeks to my father who was surprised to see how much I progressed since he last saw me. After contemplating and discussing of how I can better control my magical powers my father asked that I don’t use too much of my magic as it might easily exhaust my mana reserves too quickly and I wouldn’t have enough mana left to use to cast any spells during crucial moments through our planned assault on the castle.\n\n
        As we were preparing for the assault on the castle, my father heard from one of the members that within the depths of labyrist lies a secret room that holds a magical ring that increases one’s magical power by half their initial magical power and as such, my father suggested that we take the time to explore the dungeons of labyrist below and try to look for the ring as we would want to gain any advantage we’d need for the attack on the castle and the king’s court mage that was rumored to be the strongest mage within the kingdom’s walls.\n\n
        As the day of assaulting the castle came upon us, my father had one last request for me before we left the hideout. He asked that me and the supposedly best mage within labyrist to spar in a one on one match where we would use our abilities to incapacitate the other through the battle without any limitations, and as such, the rest of the members acted as spectators and watch over how the match between me and my opponent would come out. This served as my initiation to show that I am fully capable of wielding my magic and using it against our enemies.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="Ending1">
        I choose to agree and go with my father to the dungeon first as my mother’s safety is my utmost priority and of course, I do miss her greatly and ever since the incident that night, not seeing her has brought me nothing but anguish and sadness, as such we set off to the castle dungeons entrance and we are immediately faced with the guards protecting the entrance along with their tamed rock lizard. My father and I agree to split on taking the opposition where my father takes on the two other knights while I deal with the giant rock lizard. As we further ventured into the depths of the dungeon we encountered more and more prisoners from wounded to dead.\n\n
        This was not something I would expect to see in my life and normally seeing the sorry sights of these prisoners would be enough to make anyone break down out of fear. But I knew I did not have time to waste and so we hastened our steps toward the deeper part of the dungeon where my mother Friede was held. As we approached the part of the dungeon where my mother was supposedly held, there were less and less knights guarding the area however, there was one last dark knight patrolling the area that seemed entirely different from all the other knights we faced so far throughout the dungeon. My father recognized him and said that the knight who was clad in dark armor was called the warden, his body was constantly imbued with magic and so not any normal person can stand up against him in a duel. However I cannot allow him to stand in between me and reunite my family once again.\n\n
        As we ended the life of the warden who had been guarding the depths of the dungeon, we finally reached the cell holding my mother where we found her lying on the ground, to our relief, she was only unconscious, and so we hurriedly brought her out of the dungeon and brought her to someplace hidden where we can return when all the fighting is all over, I told my father that I alone should go to the throne room and face the king myself and that he should stay with my mother to protect her from anything that comes near. He hesitantly agrees to my decision and bids me goodluck to my battle against the king.\n\n
        As I fight my way through the knights guarding the way to the throne room through the hallway, an ominous aura continues to exude more and more as I get closer to the royal chambers. I stand in front of the door and open it slowly where I am greeted by a giant ball of flame hurled towards me. I narrowly dodged the incoming spell but was slightly burnt from the intensity of its flames. The last thing that was stopping me from standing in front of the king was the court mage who had been serving the king since his childhood. The final battle to end it once and for all. \n\n
        With the court mage now gone, I finally stood in front of the king and without letting him get any chance to fight back, I drew my sword one more time and thrust it through his chest, ending his life right then and there… I returned to where my parents were hiding and disappeared from the castle yard without a trace. The clashing of Labyrist members and knights of the king had died down until nothing but silence was left. THE END.

    </string>
    <string name="ChoiceA">
        I chose to further hone my abilities under the tutelage of my father whom I trusted the most as he was the one who saved me from when the house was on fire and the one who I believe wants to save mother the most. Since he knows me best, he’ll be able to teach me what I do right and wrong during our training sessions. The week of harsh and strict training passed by and I felt myself more confident and capable of holding my sword in a steady grip. He gave me one final test, to explore the deepest part of the Labyrist headquarter dungeons and defeat the monster guarding their armory that held their best arms and armor that can be used in battling against enemies in the castle dungeons\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="FirstPart">
        In the magical kingdom of Arlenstein where humans and monsters exist, lived a tyrannical king by the name of Cyneric Arlenstein who day by day oppressed his people. For centuries, this has been the democracy that the people were forced to follow from the kings passed down as well as the heritage that was passed on to them. This changed when one day a child by the name of Lukas was born with magical potential that far surpassed those that had previously existed. With this knowledge, a hidden resistance that went by the name of Labyrist took the child in and raised him in hopes of overthrowing the king alongside his legion of knights and monsters.\n\n
        My name is Lukas Hanleye, I was born of commoner and noble blood and had a high magical aptitude at a very young age, my father was working Harren Hanleye as a knight serving the king whilst having a loving relationship with my mother Friede Rey who was of common blood. In the kingdom of Arlenstein this was against the law, however, this did not stop them from showing their love for each other and took care of me behind the eyes of the kingdom. It was but a peaceful 13 years however, that peace did not last as the king finally noticed the suspicious movements of my father and discovered he was secretly meeting with my mother for a very long time, that night as I was lying in bed and fell asleep, I awoke to the smell of burning wood and smoke, the house that me and my mother had secretly lived in was on fire. I called out to my mother as I went down the stairs but to my surprise, she was nowhere to be found. As I was standing in the midst of the fire in shock of what was happening, I suddenly collapsed and I thought to myself, is this how it ends?\n\n
        When I came to from my slumber, I noticed that I was tied to a chair surrounded by darkness while in front of me was a hooded figure standing beside a staff with light shining upon it. I panicked and asked the hooded figure where I was, and asked where my parents were, but the figure just stood there in silence. Shortly after, the hooded figure approached me casting a spell of light and slowly removed it showing the face of my father which revealed an angry yet sorrowful man. He said Lukas, my son, I bear grave news to you, your mother was taken away by the king and brought into their deepest dungeons scheduled to be executed the next month. As I sit there in shock, I gather up my wits and ask him what happened that night and why the house was on fire to which he explained that the king had discovered the relationship he had with my mother and that by the kingdom’s laws it was forbidden thus the king ordered the arrest of him Friede and Lukas. As soon as he heard the news of the orders being brought out, he rushed to where we lived as soon as he could only to find a blazing house, in fear he found me on the floor unconscious under a wooden beam and brought me out safely to where we are now.\n\n
        He explained to me that the place we were in was the main headquarters of the hidden society of Labyrist, a society of people who bore a deep grudge towards the kingdom’s ruler, the king, Cyneric. My father revealed to me that I was a very unique and special child and that only I was capable of stopping the king and freeing the kingdom from his tyrannical reign. He said that my magical potential far surpassed those that joined since the foundation of the society itself. As we finished talking about the situation and what our positions were, he untied me and brought me beside the pedestal which held the staff and told me that with the power of the staff of aeons and my magical ability, I would be able to lead the society out of the shadows and usher on a brighter future for the nation itself. He passed on the staff to me and told me only to use the staff when I have to protect myself or someone you deem important as its power is not to be underestimated and that if it were to fall into the wrong hands, the kingdom would never again see a bright tomorrow. And so he led me out of the dark room into a much brighter lit room filled with people who held the same demeanor with one another who all held a deep grudge against the king. He introduced me to them and explained that if we were to overthrow the king, we would need all the help they can get and asked for them to teach me everything they know, specifically combat techniques and anything that could help me become a better warrior. Each of them left a different impression that showed their pains and suffering and questioned why they had to waste their time speaking with a child that could very well be dead weight. As such my father brought all of us to the sparring grounds where people could test their combat prowess and learn from each other.\n\n
        My father tossed me a dull blade and asked me to fight him to show what I was capable of. As we were preparing to fight, I remember all the lessons he taught me and the stances I needed to learn against different opponents. As my father was the one who taught me everything I knew, I didn’t expect to win against him. Before the battle started, he explained to me how magic worked and how I could harness it and use its power against my enemies and for myself. He taught me how to conjure the basic spells, flame, barrier, and heal. He told me to visualize how I wanted my magic to form itself and it would be conjured and used as I would command it to. Lastly, he explained 3 important things to me which are, when an opponent is going for a heavy attack, it is better to evade rather than block the attack, when the enemy is about to cast an elemental ability, it is better to use the barrier spell to reduce the damage as much as possible. And finally, every time I use a magical ability, it uses up my mana points which regenerate over time. with all these tips in mind our sparring battle had begun.\n\n
        After the match ended against my father in the sparring match, the spectators were all surprised by how well I was capable of handling myself against him as he used to be a knight who served under the king he told me that I had to prepare myself within 2 weeks’ time and spare no effort to become stronger in order to save my mother. He gave me the choice of;\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="ChoiceAOutcome">

        After training with his father,
        He began to descend into the dungeon to defeat the monster that was said to be guarding the entrance to the armory.
        He went through a multitude of rooms filled with traps and faced different monsters such as large rats, wandering eyebats, and rabid dire wolves.
        After getting through all the weaker monsters he finally managed to reach the room where the said monster was guarding the armory but to his surprise nothing was standing in front of the vault.
        He slowly approached the entrance to the armory and suddenly felt a cold chill wash over him and saw something dripping from the ceiling and it was none other than a brood mother,
        a giant spider that had its children fight for her as it spewed webs and acid on unaware warriors from its mandibles.
        The Prince took a quick retreat and prepared himself for the battle ahead.\n\n

        After defeating the spider, the Prince entered the armory only to find an empty room and a few seconds later,
        his father revealed himself from the shadows wielding a sheathed blade that he said was his reward for finishing the final test he had given.
        He asked his father why the King lied about the armory to which his father replied there was an armory but not anymore and didn’t elaborate any further.
        The Prince took the blade his father had given him and unsheathed it,
        the blade had rune carvings on it that meant elemental energy can be used to imbue the blade with magical powers.
        His father then said that it was his most treasured weapon and planned to give it to him when he was ready to fight for the kingdom of Arlenstein’s freedom.\n\n

        After they went back up to the main headquarters of Labyrist,
        King Cyneric and Prince Lukas continued to make more preparations for the assault on the castle which lasted for around 2 weeks of planning and training for both of them and all the other members of Labyrist.
        As the day of attacking the castle and the king had come,
        the sound of steel clashing as they dashed through the battlefield to enter the castle’s walls was a horrid and fearful sight but the Prince gather his courage and march onwards towards the goal that everyone longed for in the society of Labyrist.
        As soon as they entered the castle walls, they were immediately confronted by the knights serving the king asking them to surrender immediately or be executed on the spot,
        this however wouldn’t come to pass since they all worked too hard to see they’re plans fail.
        And so they exchanged attacks as they fought through the castle courtyard.\n\n
        I was then again faced with another decision asked by my father to accompany him to save his mother first by going through the castle dungeons before heading toward the throne room and having the final battle against King Cyneric.\n\n




    </string>
</resources>